Vasanthapoorani S

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

vasanthapoorani16@gmail.com

9159751661

linkedin.com/in/vasanthapoorani-s-1ba124178

Summary

I have good hands-on experience with various DevOps tools such as Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, GIT, Terraform, Python for scripting and Linux Operating System platforms such as Ubuntu. I have experience in java (Spring Boot framework, Spring Integration, Spring Batch).

Experience

Spring Boot Developer

Tata Consultancy Services

Oct 2020 - Present (1 year 7 months +)

- Development of REST API's in Java Spring Boot Framework
- Informatica to Java Migration using Spring Batch, Spring Integration
- Worked with Groovy for writing Test Cases
- This includes development of Dockerfile for micro-services and their deployment files

N Web Developer

Nyx Wolves

Mar 2019 - May 2019 (3 months)

I have worked in the company as a project intern for 2 months. That was such a wonderful experience indeed. I have learnt many new technologies and worked under 2 projects. I have also worked in some WordPress websites during the period.



bluCursor Infotech Pvt Ltd

Jul 2018 - Aug 2018 (2 months)

My responsibility as an intern was to perform research and add relevant data on an upcoming Q/A platform. I also did testing of the application and provided feedback to the teams.

Education

SNS College of Technology, Coimbatore

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science and Engineering 2016 - 2020

Acquired 96% First class with distinction

Bharath Montessori Matric Higher Secondary School

HSLC, Bio-Math

2014 - 2016

Skills

```
docker • Jenkins • Terraform • Kubernetes • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Linux • Java • Spring Framework • SQL • Python (Programming Language)
```

Honors & Awards

Academic Proficiency Certificate - SNS College Of Technology

Aug 2018

Scored and maintained a CGPA of over 9.5 for 5 consecutive semesters.